<map>
	<room name="Foyer">
		<description>You&apos;re in the foyer of a pretty ordinary-looking house. There&apos;s a pretty nice light fixture hanging above you,
and a large door behind you. It looks like your house, but you feel like it&apos;s not. 
The front door is locked. Might as well explore the house.
There is an exit to the north.</description>
		<exits>1 -1 -1 -1 -1 -1</exits>
	</room>
	<room name="Living Room">
		<description>It&apos;s a living room. There&apos;s a couch, coffee table, armchair, television, and coffin. It seems pretty ordinary, just like
your living room. There are some stairs, and it looks like there's a kitchen and a bedroom connecting to the living room.
There are exits to the south, east, west, and up.</description>
		<item name="Magazine">It says Britney Spears is still killing it.</item>
		<item name="Shoe">Looks just like your shoe, but it isn't your size.</item>
		<item name="Dog">Fluffy. Wait, since when were dogs allowed?</item>
		<exits>-1 0 2 3 4 -1</exits>
	</room>
	<room name="Kitchen">
		<description>The kitchen is pretty big. A huge stove, oven, and fridge. Fully stocked with pots and pans and knives. Dinner is making itself,
as if this were an ordinary day. Looks like it's making lasagna. Which is weird because usually lasagna is reserved for Christmas.
There is an exit to the west.</description>
		<item name="Knife">Looks pretty sharp.</item>
		<item name="Apple">An apple a day keeps them away.</item>
		<item name="Skull">Common cooking ingredient.</item>
		<item name="Pie">Oh boy, what flavor?"</item>
		<exits>-1 -1 -1 1 -1 -1</exits>
	</room>
	<room name="Bedroom">
		<description>The bedroom is kinda small. There is one monarch-size bed, two nightstands, two lamps, and a flashy area rug that absolutely 
does not match the rest of the decor. Girrrl. I guess most people suck at interior decorating these days. Ordinary.
There is an exit to the east.</description>
		<item name="Blanket">Warm and fluffy, like a blanket should be.</item>
		<item name="Watch">The second hand is going back and forth.</item>
		<item name="Sword">Looks freshly sharpened.</item>
		<item name="Pillow">There's an ugly pillow cover on it that matches the rug.</item>
		<exits>-1 -1 1 -1 -1 -1</exits>
	</room>
	<room name="Upstairs">
		<description>It is pretty light upstairs as there are many windows. It looks like kids use this as a play room. Everything seems ordinary.
There are Hot Wheels, Legos, grenades, Barbies, etc all over the floor. The computer desk looks interesting, at least.
There is an exit downwards.</description>
		<item name="Toy car">Kachow.</item>
		<item name="Barbie">Her hand is missing.</item>
		<item name="Puzzle piece">Someone is very upset about completing the puzzle this belongs to.</item>
		<item name="Key">Maybe it opens the front door?</item>
		<item name="Play-Doh">A snack.</item>
		<exits>-1 -1 -1 -1 -1 1</exits>
	</room>
</map>